



### **About Me**

A highly resourceful,innovative and competent PHP Laravel developer having a good grip on design and coding of web applications built in php laravel. Possessing considerable knowledge of the development of web applications keeping the code convention and harmony in mind using php and mysql. Having good experience in developing apps like social apps,marketplace apps,ecommerce and having an ambition to complete projects to the highest standard.

## **Work Experience**

### Feb.2022-Present TeekIT.co PHP Laravel Developer

- troubleshoot,test and maintained the core product.
- Co-Ordinated with co-developers.
- Upgraded app to Latest version.
- Created Apis to be consumed by app developers.

#### 2021-Feb,2022 **Teratone PHP Laravel Developer**

- Worked closely with project manager and mobile app developers to design apis according to their needs and made sure they're being consumed correctly.
- Strong optimization of functionality.
- Contributed in phases of development lifecycle.

### Oct,2022-Jan,2021 Maniwebify **PHP Internship**

- Development and implementation of design.
- Developing logic for new and existing features.
- · Working closely with the company's web team, enabling them to meet their objectives.

# **Expertise**

- PHP
- Laravel
- MySQL
- API
- Ajax
- ¡Query
- HTML5
- CSS
- Bootstrap

### Education

2016-2020 **Bsc Software Engineering** 

Univeristy Of Science & Technology Bannu 4 years

2014-2016 Pre-engineering

Govt Post Graduate College Bannu 2 years

## Languages

- English
- Urdu

# **Work Samples**

- Teekit co uk
- 97tibo.com
- barqraftar.pk